



CONTACT





gabaiz88@gmail.com







https://github.com/gabaiz88



LANGUAGES



- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- NODE.JS
- JAVA
- GITHUB
- SOL
- C#
- C++
- PHOTOSHOP

GABRIEL AIZMAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ANALYST **WEB DEVELOPER**

ABOUT

For the last 2 years, I have been involved in programming languages such as JAVA, JAVASCRIPT, HTML, CSS, SASS and C#.

Prior to this, I worked in the banking and financial sector for over 14 years. These roles allowed me to develop leadership and management skills, as well as effective communication and collaboration skills. I am used to remaining calm while working in high pressure environments, and I have strong problem-solving skills.

In the last year I studied and trained in the IT area, by taking Web Development courses, as well as undertaking the Systems Analyst career in ORT Institute in Buenos Aires.

I'm looking for a new challenge that would allow me to further develop my system analyst skills.



EXPERIENCE

-HEAD TELLER - BRANCH OPERATIONS **MANAGER**

Mar 2020 - Aug 2022

Banco Credicoop Coop. Ltdo.

-BANK TELLER

Jun 2014 - Mar 2020

Banco Credicoop Coop. Ltdo.

-CREDIT RISK ANALYST

Dec 2012 - Jun 2014

Metropolis Cia. Financiera

-HEAD TELLER

May 2010 - Dec 2012

Metropolis Cia. Financiera



EDUCATION

-ORT INSTITUTE ARGENTINA

Aug 2021 - Present

SYSTEMS ANALYST

-CODER HOUSE

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

JAVASCRIPT

Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

WEB DEVELOPER